
	<rss version="2.0">
		<channel>
		<title>Fimoculous.com</title>
		<description>Feeding On Itself</description>
		<copyright>Rex Sorgatz</copyright> 
		<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/</link>
		<language>en-us</language> 
		<ttl>60</ttl>
			
			<item>
				<title>Encyclopedia of Misinformation</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7204.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.amazon.com/Encyclopedia-Misinformation-Counterfeits-Confabulations-Miscellaneous/dp/141972911X/ref=nosim/fimoculouscom-20/"><img height="434" width="340" src="http://www.fimoculous.com/images/misinfo-cover.jpg" align="right" height="638" width="500" alt="misinfo" /></a>I have a book coming out at the end of this month! If you once enjoyed this blog, you will likely find <em><a href="https://www.amazon.com/Encyclopedia-Misinformation-Counterfeits-Confabulations-Miscellaneous/dp/141972911X/ref=nosim/fimoculouscom-20/">The Encyclopedia of Misinformation</a></em> a delight. It was influenced greatly by blog culture of early '00s.]]></description>
				<category>internal</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>Netflix and Ch-Ch-Chilly</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7203.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://backchannel.com/the-internet-really-has-changed-everything-here-s-the-proof-928eaead18a8"><img src="http://www.fimoculous.com/images/boy-fishing.jpg" align="right" height="226" width="340" alt="Ice Fishing in Napoleon" /></a></p>
<p><a href="https://backchannel.com/the-internet-really-has-changed-everything-here-s-the-proof-928eaead18a8"><b>Netflix and Ch-Ch-Chilly</b></a><br/>
How have decades of mass media and technology changed us? I return to my hometown to find answers.<p>]]></description>
				<category>internal</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>Art Authenticity</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7202.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><em>Oh good, the login to the CMS I wrote in 2001 still works!</em></p>

<p>Just a note -- I have been doing a series on Medium about art authenticity in the age of the copy. Here are all the links in one place:</p>

<hr style="width: 230px; margin: 20px 0 30px 150px;"/>

<p><a href="https://medium.com/message/this-is-not-a-vermeer-67b752b150c0" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.fimoculous.com/images/girl.png" align="right" width="340" alt="Girl" /></a>

<strong><a href="https://medium.com/message/this-is-not-a-vermeer-67b752b150c0" target="_blank">Part 1: This Is Not a Vermeer <sup>TM</sup></a></strong><br />Can anyone own a masterpiece? Five very dissimilar people share a common desire: To own a Vermeer.</p>

<hr style="width: 230px; margin: 20px 0 30px 150px;"/>

<p><a href="https://medium.com/message/uber-for-art-forgeries-2c9c8bf41608" target="_blank"><img src="https://d262ilb51hltx0.cloudfront.net/max/2000/1*auozMtphAegSNcbfx4JvmQ.gif" align="right" width="340" alt="Replicants" /></a>

<strong><a href="https://medium.com/message/uber-for-art-forgeries-2c9c8bf41608" target="_blank">Part 2: Uber for Art Forgeries</a></strong><br />So you want to own a masterpiece? It's easy! In part two in this series about artistic authenticity, we explore how to score that painting you have always wanted. </p>

<hr style="width: 230px; margin: 20px 0 30px 150px;"/>

<p><a href="https://medium.com/message/forgeries-gone-wild-d9b4c195da5" target="_blank"><img src="https://d262ilb51hltx0.cloudfront.net/max/1000/1*zrn9_arMd2kBJ8zlFdeDnA.gif" align="right" width="340" alt="Fake" /></a>

<strong><a href="https://medium.com/message/forgeries-gone-wild-d9b4c195da5" target="_blank">Part 3: Forgeries Gone Wild!</a></strong><br />How widespread is art forgery? Experts say it's wildly rampant. Is it time to reconsider the economy of images?</p>

<hr style="width: 230px; margin: 20px 0 30px 150px;"/>

<p><a href="https://medium.com/message/the-end-of-authentication-cbbfbcb0c49e" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.fimoculous.com/images/the-procuress-photoshop.png" align="right" width="340" alt="Procuress" /></a>

<strong><a href="https://medium.com/message/the-end-of-authentication-cbbfbcb0c49e" target="_blank">Part 4: The End of Authentication</a></strong><br />Woo-hoo! You just discovered a Vermeer in your aunts basement. But who will verify if it is real? Maybe no one.</p>

<hr style="width: 230px; margin: 20px 0 30px 150px;"/>

<p><a href="https://medium.com/message/the-artist-the-thief-the-forger-and-her-lover-49dc3df79610" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.fimoculous.com/images/howtosteal1.jpg" align="right" width="340" alt="Steal" /></a>

<strong><a href="https://medium.com/message/the-artist-the-thief-the-forger-and-her-lover-49dc3df79610" target="_blank">Part 5: The Artist, the Thief, the Forger, and Her Lover</a></strong><br />How did the <em>Mona Lisa</em> become famous? The biggest art heist of all time connects the forger and the thief.</p>]]></description>
				<category>internal</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>VIEWSOURCE</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7201.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[If you're looking for something new from me, I've started a new site called <a href="http://viewsource.tv/" target="_blank">VIEWSOURCE</a>, where I write about one piece of video every day.]]></description>
				<category>tv</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>On Bullshit: The Newsroom</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7200.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://www.fimoculous.com/images/bullshit1.png" align="right" height="227" width="340" alt="bullshit" /></p>
<p>We're now two episodes into <em>The Newsroom</em>, HBO's newest entry in chatter-inducing Sunday programming. <a href="http://www.metacritic.com/tv/the-newsroom">Reviews</a> of the show have been <a href="http://www.newyorker.com/arts/critics/television/2012/06/25/120625crte_television_nussbaum?currentPage=all">brutal</a>, but asking a media critic to judge this show is like asking a cannibal how his gallbladder tastes. Outside of media circles (amongst the vegans, to continue this overwrought metaphor), the show seems somewhat more widely appreciated.</p>

<p>This phenomena fascinates me. We seem to have some sort of uncanny valley relationship to art. If we are extremely close to it -- if the subject matter is <em>about us</em> -- then it is very likely that we find the similarity ugly, a disfigured clone of ourselves. The entertainment landscape is littered with examples of subcultures (professions, geographies, lifestyles) disagreeing with how they are portrayed by mainstream art.<sup>1</sup> It makes you wonder: When does a subculture actually ever like art about itself?<sup>2</sup></p>

<p>The anxiety in appreciating art about oneself probably involves some deep Lacanian mirror stage shit. Or maybe it's dormroom pop psych: We are apprehensive about the shortcuts that art must take. We don't enjoy having our subcultures portrayed because it reduces ideas down to sketches, people down to characters. Local significance loses to storyline, depth loses to drama.</p>

<p><em>So duh</em>, of course we media people hate <em>The Newsroom</em>. It's characters don't act like our colleagues, it's fantasies aren't our realities. So what? Part of me wants to say, <em>fuck it, that's our problem, not Sorkin's</em>. But other times, I'm like, <em>wait, that's fucking bullshit</em>.</p>

<p>I want to talk about the part that's bullshit.</p>

<p>I worked in newsrooms for over 10 years, most of the time at websites attached to TV stations or networks. I've seen, and usually participated in, the creation of news around executions in Texas, riots in Seattle, hurricanes in Florida, and psychotic killing sprees in Virginia.  </p>

<p>What I offer here is not an artistic or moral assessment of <em>The Newsroom</em>. Despite having nuanced qualitative opinions about the show<sup>3</sup>, that's not what we'll be discussing here. Let's temporarily ignore the finer ethical and aesthetic points, which are usually finessed as blustery diatribes, and instead focus on what's believable.</p>

<p>What's bullshit, and what's not?</p>

<p><strong>That eruption from Will McAvoy in the first scene.</strong> Yeah, this is kinda bullshit. It's easy to imagine an Olbermann-like figure doing this (actually, that's <em>all</em> he did), but it's pretty unimaginable for a Brian Williams or a Katie Couric. Or maybe our hero is supposed to be more like Dylan Rattigan or Rachel Maddow? Actually, who knows! The way this show blurs the monolithic network anchor with the opinionated cable host is precisely the kind of fake construction that feels like bullshit. Or as <a href="http://www.colbertnation.com/">the greatest news anchor of our time</a> would say, a great moment of <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Truthiness">truthiness</a>. </p>

<p><strong>Having a blog.</strong> Not bullshit. Olbermann had one, Maddow has <a href="http://maddowblog.msnbc.msn.com/">one</a>, Brian Williams has <a href="http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/30622506/">a</a> <a href="http://dailynightly.msnbc.msn.com/">couple</a>, Tucker Carlson has <a href="http://dailycaller.com/">a whole goddamn site</a>.</p>

<p><strong>Not knowing you have a blog.</strong> Complete bullshit. This portrait of social media ignorance would have been accurate 10 years ago, but television executives started to freak out about the internet a while ago. They've spent an immense amount of time catching up, so now they're better at Twitter than you.</p>

<p><strong>Walking into a newsroom and yelling "Punjab" to the Southeast Asian character that you know isn't named Punjab.</strong> This would never happen, even if your name is Sean Hannity. Bullshit.</p>

<p><strong>Calling out someone as a "sorority girl."</strong> Sensing we would deem this bullshit, <a href="http://gawker.com/5921033/aaron-sorkin-calls-female-reporter-internet-girl-is-a-condescending-prick/">Sorkin set out to prove it's not</a>.</p>

<p><strong>Dating people you work with.</strong> Not bullshit. The only professionals who fuck each other more are actors.</p>

<p><strong>Arguing with people you date while you're working.</strong> Not bullshit. The only professionals who argue with each other more are politicians.</p>

<p><strong>The speech from an Executive Producer about fearing Halliburton and the lawsuit it would bring.</strong> Bullshit. I don't know a reporter who wouldn't love to catch Halliburton, Scientology, or whatever big scary corporate entity you name. The mere fact that <em>Time-Warner-owned HBO aired this scene</em> seems to completely undermine any truth it is seeking to reveal.</p>

<p><strong>Hiring a new Executive Producer without telling the anchor.</strong> I would say this is bullshit, but I've recently heard a story similar to this. Judgement: perhaps not bullshit.</p>

<p><strong>Running to your agent when the President of News hires an Executive Producer over the top of you.</strong> Yeah, they're prima donnas, so this could happen. Not necessarily bullshit.</p>

<p><strong>The ongoing debate between popularity and quality.</strong> This would never be said aloud. However, it subliminally infuses every newsroom decision. Pseudo-bullshit.</p>

<p><strong>Forgetting the name of your hot blonde assistant.</strong> If this show is actually modelled on Olbermann, then this is bullshit. He'd never forget that.</p>

<p><strong>Having a President of News who is drunk "most of the time" at work.</strong> Being a heavy drinker can still be romanticized within some media circles (especially if you hang out with bloggers), but being regularly drunk at work would simply not be permitted any more, at any level. Drink up, that's bullshit. </p>

<p><strong>Quoting <em>Don Quixote</em>.</strong> Bullshit.</p>

<p><strong>Quoting <em>Man of La Mancha</em>.</strong> Epic bullshit, <em>fa la la la la</em>.</p>

<p><strong>Vacationing in Saint Lucia with Erin Andrews.</strong> Questionable bullshit.</p>

<p><strong>Figuring out the oil spill that quickly.</strong> This is probably the single most annoying thing in the first episodes. If you remember the evolution of the oil spill story, it took weeks for scientists to figure out what our Happy Band of Googlers sleuthed out in a few hours. Complete media fantasy bullshit. </p>

<p><strong>An executive producer threatening an anchor with a fake on-air graphic seconds before going live.</strong> Reminiscent of both <em>Broadcast News</em> and <em>Network</em>, this nifty dramatic effect was as much bullshit then as it is now.</p>

<p><strong>Not knowing where your control room is.</strong> Crazy bullshit. </p>

<p><strong>FOX News hiring someone with three Mohammeds in his name.</strong> Pass.</p>

<p><strong>Sending an email that accidentally goes to 178,000 people.</strong> Yep, bullshit. Of course email groups like that exist, but they were introduced to corporations 10 years ago, not last year. So not only does everyone know how they work, but we all also know that not everyone has access to email all those lists. A reply-all snafu would have been less bullshitty.</p>

<p><strong>A fluff newsreader with a PhD in Economics from Duke and an adjunct professor at Columbia.</strong> Sure, this is supposed to be Erin Burnett, but still bullshit! She's barely old enough to have a PhD.</p>

<p><strong>The Three I's.</strong> That kind of bullshit would actually happen, so it's not bullshit.</p>

<p><strong>Minutes after delivering the sanctimonious Three I's, commenting on a reporters legs.</strong> B-------.</p>

<p><strong>The organization of this network.</strong> This is one of the more perplexing elements of the show. ACN is apparently a 24-hour cable news outlet, but this show gets the network treatment. Cable newsrooms are much more fluid than this show suggests, with more interaction of programming and personnel between shows. </p>

<p><strong>Hiding under a bed while your date fucks his ex-girlfriend.</strong> I have less expertise on this matter, so I'll let you call this one.</p>

<p>So?</p>

<p>Correlating quality with verisimilitude is always a dicey proposition<sup>4</sup>. But when a show places itself into history with real news events, and within a professional industry whose mandate is exposing truth, <em>The Newsroom</em> must be aware that it has put itself under the lens of realism's scrutiny. </p>

<p><em>The Newsroom</em> rubs so close to reality that it makes you wonder how Will McAvoy would feel about it. After a long walk, some nifty orchestration, and a verbose conclusion, he'd enter his closing judgement into the chryon: It's bullshit.</p>

<p><b>Footnotes</b></p>

<p><sup>1</sup> For example, I lived in Fargo when the movie <em>Fargo</em> came out. To this day, the city has an extremely antagonistic relationship toward their portrayal as noble unsavages with snowboots. <br/>
<sup>2</sup> The answer? Lawyers always love seeing themselves.<br/>
<sup>3</sup> It's bullshit.<br/>
<sup>4</sup> Didn't those dragons in <em>Game of Thrones</em> grow up just a little too quickly?<br/></p>]]></description>
				<category>tv</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>Ad Tracking Present</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7199.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2012/02/im-being-followed-how-google-and-104-other-companies-are-tracking-me-on-the-web/253758/" target="_blank">I'm Being Followed: How Google -- and 104 Other Companies -- Are Tracking Me on the Web</a>. Just read it. It's great.]]></description>
				<category>ads</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>TED Talk from 2023</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7198.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[This make-believe TED Talk from 2023, done in conjuncture with Ridley Scott's new film <a href="http://www.prometheus-movie.com/" target="_blank"><em>Prometheus</em></a>, reminds me of <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OQDBhg60UNI" target="_blank">EPIC</a>.
<object width='524' height='374'><param name='movie' value='http://video.ted.com/assets/player/swf/EmbedPlayer.swf'></param><param name='allowFullScreen' value='true' /><param name='wmode' value='transparent'></param><param name='bgColor' value='#ffffff'></param><param name='flashvars' value='vu=http://video.ted.com/talks/ads/postrolls/Prometheus/Prometheus-450k.mp4&su=http://images.ted.com/images/ted/tedindex/embed-posters/Prometheus-TED-embed.jpg&vw=512&vh=288&ap=0'/><embed src='http://video.ted.com/assets/player/swf/EmbedPlayer.swf' pluginspace='http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer' type='application/x-shockwave-flash' wmode='transparent' bgColor='#ffffff' width='524' height='374' allowFullScreen='true' flashvars='vu=http://video.ted.com/talks/ads/postrolls/Prometheus/Prometheus-450k.mp4&su=http://images.ted.com/images/ted/tedindex/embed-posters/Prometheus-TED-embed.jpg&vw=512&vh=288&ap=0'></embed></object>
<p><a href="http://blog.ted.com/2012/02/28/writing-a-tedtalk-from-the-future-q-a-with-damon-lindelof/" target="_blank">More info</a>.</p>]]></description>
				<category>film</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>The Future is the Pseudo-Algrorithm</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7197.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[Compare: <a href="http://gawker.com/5887697/how-i-found-the-human-being-behind-horseebooks-the-internets-favorite-spambot" target="_blank">Gawker's story</a> about <a href="https://twitter.com/#!/horse_ebooks" target="_blank">Horse_ebooks</a> and <a href="http://shortformblog.tumblr.com/post/18230584617/youtube-reply-girls-seo" target="_blank">Shortformblog's story</a> about <a href="http://www.youtube.com/user/MeganSpeaks" target="_blank">reply girls</a>. Once again, spammers are ahead of the curve in predicting the future of the internets: <strong><em>The Pseudo-Algorithmic Human!</em></strong>]]></description>
				<category>online</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>When We Build</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7196.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[This is from a couple months ago, but I just found it now, and it's amazing:
<p><a href="http://vimeo.com/34017777">Wilson Miner - When We Build</a></p>
<p><iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/34017777?title=0&byline=0&portrait=0" width="400" height="225" frameborder="0" webkitAllowFullScreen mozallowfullscreen allowFullScreen></iframe></p>]]></description>
				<category>design</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>Maybe Panther Town</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7195.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[In a recent episode of the WTF podcast, <a href="http://www.wtfpod.com/podcast/episodes/episode_252_-_bill_lawrence" target="_blank">Bill Lawrence</a> (the creator of <em>Scrubs</em>, <em>Cougar Town</em>, and <em>Spin City</em>) talks about how he hates the name of his show <em>Cougar Town</em> so much that he considered changing it this season. One of the main reasons he didn't is that DVRs aren't equipped to understand a name change, so the show would essentially lose any audience that had a season pass in TiVo. 

<p>Anyway, it got me thinking: Has there ever been a successful show that changed its name?</p>]]></description>
				<category>tv</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>I Will Always Google You</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7194.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[The weird personal thing for me about this clip of Chris Cornell performing "I Will Always Love You" is that I found it playing around with the YouTube app on my GoogleTV.
<iframe width="560" height="315" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/vgFAq9Q8l8U" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
				<category>music</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>Startup Threads Monthly</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7193.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[Remember <a href="http://techcrunch.com/2006/05/04/get-web-20-schwag-from-valleyschwag/" target="_blank">Valleyschwag</a>, the site that sent you a monthly package of promotional material from hot startups? The idea is back with <a href="https://www.startupthreadsmonthly.com/" target="_blank">Startup Threads Monthly</a>, which sends you a monthly t-shirt from a startup. So far, it has included Boxee, Twilio, Reddit, and BreadPig.]]></description>
				<category>tshirts</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>The Game Is Rigged</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7192.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[Rick says a bunch of interesting things in <a href="http://www.betabeat.com/2012/02/14/friends-investing-in-friends-when-it-comes-to-startups-is-the-fix-already-in/" target="_blank">his new column</a> about whether you need to a be highly networked individual to succeed online. I especially relish how he ties geography into the conversation, alluding to a midwestern startup.

<blockquote>And many, many more hyper-social New Yorkers and San Franciscans make successful startups than antisocial Midwesterners. Or even antisocial New Yorkers. These are things you can control. You can move to San Francisco. Better yet, you can move to New York. You can go to meetups. You can go to conferences. You can email investors. You can go to classes at General Assembly. It's in your control. Or, you can stay at home in the Midwest, reading TechCrunch and talking about how it's all rigged and an insiders game.</blockquote>

<p>This will frustrate my friends in Minneapolis -- those dozens of startups trying to compete at <a href="http://cocomsp.com/" target="_blank">CoCo</a> and other places. They're trying to create their own scene right now. Creative acts are becoming increasingly dependent on groups of people. Being part of a "scene" in music was undeniably important in the '80s and '90s, but now it's become as true for fashion, technology, theater, and nearly all creative arts.</p>

<p>It's an interesting dilemma building a company in the midwest: Your success is as much a factor of your peers' success -- the community's success -- as it is the brilliance and execution of your idea.</p>]]></description>
				<category>online</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>All This Talk of Cookies Is Making Me Hungry</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7191.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[<a href="http://online.wsj.com/article_email/SB10001424052970204880404577225380456599176-lMyQjAxMTAyMDEwNjExNDYyWj.html#project%3DSAFARITRACKINGCODE0212%26articleTabs%3Dinteractive" target="_blank">Most detailed code-driven infographic in the mainstream press ever?</a>]]></description>
				<category>tech</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
			<item>
				<title>Martin Amis' Guide to Games</title>
				<link>http://www.fimoculous.com/archive/post-7190.cfm</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
				<description><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.themillions.com/2012/02/the-arcades-project-martin-amis-guide-to-classic-video-games.html" target="_blank">Martin Amis wrote a guide to Space Invaders in the '80s</a>.]]></description>
				<category>games</category>
				 <author>rex@fimoculous.com</author> 
			</item>
			
		</channel>
	</rss>
	
